# Juan Lemos

Personal Information Name: Juan Lemos Web: <u>juanlemos.com</u>

<u>linkedin.com/in/juan-lemos</u>



## Summary

Software engineer graduated from Universidad Católica del Uruguay. Passionate about learning, making questions and solving problems. Interested in decision making and business management. I have worked for more than 2 years into the software development industry with American clients, in diverse teams. My tasks has been to align the software solutions with the client's needs and thinking in the medium- and long-term consequences.

### Skills

#### Programming:

- React
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- NodeJS
- SQL
- Android
- Java
- Swift

#### Others:

- English
- Portuguese
- **Decision** making
- Communication
- **Problem-Solving**

## Experience

Full stack developer at Código Del Sur Aug 2017 - Present

Scholarship at ICT4V (Information and Communication Technologies for Verticals) Sep 2016 - Jul 2017

### Education

IEEM Business school – PJP business programs 2019

Universidad Católica Del Uruguay – Computer engineer 2013 - 2017